<?xml version='1.0' standalone='yes'?>
<questions>
    <question>
        <q>
           Công ty bạn có muốn tính giá thành trên từng MO? (chi phí nguyên vật liệu trực tiếp, chi phí nhân công , chi phí overhead)
            . Chi phí nhân công và overhead sẽ được update dựa trên thời gian làm việc của work order? Cuối tháng có cần update lại chi phí nhân công và chi phí overhead không?
        </q>

        <a>

        </a>
    </question>

    <question>
        <q>
            Bạn có muốn cancel và set draft một MO đã done không?
        </q>

        <a>
            100
            90
            82
        </a>
    </question>
    <question>
        <q>
            Bạn có muốn update lại giá thành của sản phẩm dựa trên BOM không?
        </q>
        <a>
            - The first supplier in the list
            - The one with smallest delivery lead time
            - The one with the smallest price
        </a>
    </question>

    <question>
        <q>
            I manage a product whose cost is based on "Standar price". Suppose I have 8 pieces of product in stock with
            a cost of 100EUR/piece. If I purchase and received two new pieces for apice of 10 EUR/piece. If I purchase
            an receive two new pieces for a price of 10 EUR/ piece , what will be my cost?
        </q>
        <a>
            100
            90
            82
        </a>
    </question>

    <question>
        <q>
            What is the impact of setting the "Control Policy" On the product as "On ordered quantities"?
        </q>
        <a>
            - when creating a vendor bill, the price comes from the purchase order, and the quantity form the reception
            - When a purchase order is confirmed, a vendor bill is automatically created
            - When creating a vendor bill, quantities and prices are automatically filled with the ordered ones

        </a>
    </question>
    <question>
        <q>
            What is the impact of setting the "Control Policy" on the product as "On ordered quantities"?
        </q>
        <a>
            - When creatign a vendor bill, the price comes from the purchase order, and the quantity from the reception
            - When a purchase order is confirmed, a vendor bill is automatically created
            - When creating a vendor bill, quantities and prices are automatically filled with the ordered ones
        </a>
    </question>

    <question>
        <q>
            Where is the costing method defined?
        </q>
        <a>
            - On the product
            - On the product category
            - On the company ( all the products have same costing method)
        </a>
    </question>

    <question>
        <q>
            When setting Quantities "Usign quantities of agreements" on an agreement type , when a request for quotation
            is generated (49:37)
        </q>
        <a>
            - The quantity is set to 0 by default
            - The quantity in RFQ can not be changed
            - The quantity in RFQ can still be changed
        </a>
    </question>

    <question>
        <q>
            Can I create a vendor bill grouping several purchase orders
        </q>
        <a>
            Yes
            No
        </a>
    </question>
    <question>
        <q>
            When a Purchase Order is validated , is it still possible to add purchase order lines?
        </q>

        <a>
            - Yes, a long as the Purchase order is not "Locked"
            - No, never
        </a>
    </question>
    <question>
        <q>
            Which of the following statements is true regarding this computation?
            (51:01)
        </q>
        <a>
            - For customers associated with this pricelist, I allow a reduction of exactly 10% on all products
            - For customer associated with this pricelist, all price will end in ".90"
            - For customers associated with this pricelist, all prices will end in ".00"

        </a>
    </question>

    <question>
        <q>
            What does it means if the forecasted quantit of a stockable product is less than the quantity on hand ?
            routes : tick on buy check box
        </q>
        <a>
            - If there is a reordering rule set, the product will be manufactured once the rule is triggered
            - The product will be ordered from a vendor everytime a sales or manufacturing order is validated
            - The product will be manufactured everytime a sales or manufacturing order is validated

        </a>
    </question>

    <question>
        <q>
            What is the "Customer lead time" field used for on the product form?
        </q>
        <a>
            - If computes the order date based on the quotation date
            - If computes the delivery order date when the quotation is confirmed
            - It is displayed in the TermConditions of the quotation
        </a>
    </question>
    <question>
        <q>
            What is the goal of the "Stock input/Output Account fields on a product category form? (53:13)
        </q>
        <a>
            - There accoutns are used to track where each product is
            - These accounts are used to track import (input) and export (output ) values of products
            - These accounts are used to track changes of inventory valuation in accounting

        </a>
    </question>
    <question>
        <q>
            Can any product be used in a sales order?
        </q>
        <a>
            - Yes, you can find all your products
            - No, you can only find products you currently have in stock
            - No, you can only find products for which you have mark as "Can be sold"
        </a>
    </question>

    <question>
        <q>
            How could I prevent a specific product form being used in quotes?
        </q>
        <a>
            - By archieving the product
            - By setting a blocking warning
            -Both solutions are correct
        </a>
    </question>

    <question>
        <q>
            what i the relation between the commitment date of a sales order and the delivery date of its delivery
            order?
        </q>
        <a>
            - Delivery date = commitment date
            - Delivery date = Commitment daet e+ product lead time
            - Delivery date = Commitment date - Product liead time
        </a>
    </question>

</questions>



